Guide to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Photographs, 1914-present CTC.1966.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Productions, 1938-2011; I.; 1021.0 photographs
  - Camelot, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph from Valley Players of Ligonier's production of Camelot including Coleen Dean and Joe Comm.
  - Can-Can, Aug. 1-2, 1974; 3.0 photographs
    This folder contains three photographs of the Oliver Plaza Dinner Theatre production of Can-Can. The second photo includes Josie Jutsie.
  - Candide, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Marcus Lovett. This Carnegie Mellon University Repertory Theatre production was performed at Hartwood Acres.
  - Carmilla's Kiss, 2001; 2.0 photographs
    Carmilla's Kiss was presented by the Edgar Allen Poe Theatre Company in August 2001, at the Gemini Theatre. These photographs include actors Joe Keenan as the vampire hunter, Lori Maxwell as the Countess, and Stacy Bartlebaugh-Gmys as Carmilla. Photographs are by George Mendel.
  - Carnival, 1982; 1.0 photograph
    Carnival was presented by the Civic Light Opera from August 3-8, 1982.
  - Carousel - Carnegie Mellon University, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    Carousel was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from February 9 - 19, 1978 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph is of Sandra Bogan and Glenn Morrissey.
  - Carousel - Civic Light Opera, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    Carousel was presented by the Civic Light Opera from July 11-16, 1978 at Heinz Hall. This photograph is of two men assembling the carousel for the play's set.
  - Carried Away, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Carried Away was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from April 14-23, 1983 by the Scotch n' Soda Club. This photograph is of Eric Reibling and Sharon Reidbord.
  - Caught in the Net, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    Caught in the Net was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 20 - September 1, 2002. Photograph is of Nick Ruggeri and Douglas Rees.
  - Celebration, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    Celebration was presented by Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from June 2-11, 1977. Photograph is of Chris Clark, JoEllen Sharp, Lou Valenzi, and Robert Devlin.
  - Celebration '76, 1976; 3.0 photographs
    This Don Brockett production was performed at the Green Gables Restaurant's Tuscany Room during 1975 and 1976. Photos include actors Pam Klinger, Larry Broadright, Bob Boyle, and Tredessa Dalton.
  - The Celestial Social Service, 2004; 1.0 photograph
    The Celestial Social Service was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from May 21 - June 6, 2004. Photograph is of Ross Blumen and Megan May.
  - That Championship Season, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    That Championship Season was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from June 29 - July 11, 1976 at the Kresge Theatre. This photograph shows Curt Williams, John Hallow, Donald Woods, Ed Rombola, and Eddie Jones.
  - Chapter Two - Mountain Playhouse, 2003; 1.0 photograph
    Chapter Two was presented by Mountain Playhouse from Jun 17-29, 2003. Photograph is of Nick Ruggeri and Janet Dickinson.
  - Chapter Two - Robert Morris College, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Chapter Two was presented by Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from July 21-30, 1983. Photograph is of Bruce Stigers and Victoria Falce.
  - Charley's Aunt - Community College of Allegheny County, July 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Charley's Aunt was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County on July 6, 1984. Photograph is of Barbara Hyland and Dale Lancaster.
  - Charley's Aunt - Robert Morris College, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    Charley's Aunt was presented by Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from July 16-18, 1981. Photograph is of Matthew Lohle and Susan Knapik.
  - Charlie and Algernon, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Charlie and Algernon was presented by Duquesne University from November 2-5, 1983. Photograph is of Joseph Disalle and Jane Marie Scutieri.
  - Cheaters, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Cheaters was presented by South Park Conservatory Theatre from June 17 - July 3, 1983. Photograph is of Sam Lane, Jerry Morris, Katie Murray, and Ruth Collura.
  - Chicago, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    In this file is one photograph of actors in Pittsburgh Musical Theater's production of Chicago. The play was performed at the Byham Theater January 23rd through February 2nd, 2002. Appearing the photo are Jeffrey Howell, Joe Franze, Kathy Lash-Fuller, Peggy Taphorn, and Allison Cahill.
  - A Chorus Line, 1980; 10.0 photographs
    A Chorus Line was presented by the Civic Light Opera from June 25 - July 13, 1980. Photographs are of cast members including Ron Kuhlman, Kay Cole, Wayne Cilento, Baayork Lee, Michel Stuart, Donna McKeehnie, Carole Bishop, Thomas Walsh, Nancy Lane, Patricia Garland, Ronald Dennis, Don Percassi, Renee Baughman, Pamela Blair, Cameron Mason, Sammy Williams, and Priscilla Lopez.
  - The Chosen, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    The Chosen was presented by the City Theatre from April 23 - May 23, 1999. Photograph is of Jesse Bernstein and Sam Henderson.
  - Cloud Nine, February 1997; 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Carnegie Mellon's production of Cloud Nine. Appearing in the photo are actors Doug Howe, Chae Lian, Mark Engelhardt, Cody Nickell, and James Babson. The production was staged at the Kresge Theatre, February 14-22, 1997.
  - The Clouds, 1979; 4.0 photographs
    The Clouds was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County from October 6-15, 1979. Photographs are of Craig Granberg, Russ Rusiski, D.E. Jukes, Mary Beth Munroe, Frances Malarky, Marykay Hensler, and Sue Huffman.
  - The Columbia Encyclopedia Presents Mary Stuart, Queen of Scotland, 1980; 1.0 photograph
    The Columbia Encyclopedia Presents Mary Stuart, Queen of Scotland was presented by the Pittsburgh Metropolitan Stage Company from February 21 - March 15, 1980. Photograph is of Shirley Tannenbaum and Jim Boerlin.
  - Come Back to the Five & Dime, Jimmy Dean, Jimmy Dean, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Come Back to the Five & Dime, Jimmy Dean, Jimmy Dean was presented by Chatham College on March 11 and 12, 1983 at the Eddy Theatre. This photograph is of DJean Rohach and Deidre Cramer.
  - Comedy of Errors, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    Comedy of Errors was presented by the Pittsburgh City Players from July 9 - August 13, 1976. Photograph is of Gela Jacobson.
  - Comic Potential, May 2002; 1.0 photograph
    Comic Potential was performed by the Little Lake Theatre Company in May 2002. The photograph shows two unidentified members of the cast.
  - Company, January 1994; 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Comtra Theatre's production of Company. Appearing in the photo are actors Dan Smith as Larry, Margie Dagenherd as Joanne, and Chris Stachtiaris as Bobby. The play was performed in January, 1994.
  - Constant Star, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    Constant Star was presented by the City Theatre Company May 30th through June 30th, 2002. This photograph includes actress Nadiyah S. Dorsey as Ida B. Wells. Photographs are by Ric Evans.
  - Cops, November 1980; 1.0 photograph
    This photograph shows cast members of Cops. Included in the photos are Robert Koch, Bonnie Gilmore, and Fred Donatelli. The Fine Line Theatre Company play was performed at the Soho Theatre in Oakland November 7-30, 1979.
  - The Cowardly Way Out, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Oliver Plaza Dinner Theatre's production of The Cowardly Way Out including Richard Locke, Marilyn O'Connell, and Charles Altma.
  - Crazy for You, October 1996; 2.0 photographs
    These photographs show cast members Melissa Bell, Jeremy Czarniak, Lenora Nemetz, John Holt, and Christopher Equizi. Gargaro Productions' Crazy for You was at the Byham Theater, October 2-8, 1996.
  - Crimes of the Heart, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Michele DiMaso and Shawn Ebbert. This University of Pittsburgh Theatre production was performed at the Pit in Oakland.
  - The Crucible, 2006; 15.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    This file contains a CD-R disc with 15 images from the Quantum Theatre production of Arthur Miller's The Crucible. The play was performed July 27th through August 20th, 2006 in Mellon Park. The images show actors Ilana Niernberger, Hugo Armstrong, Robin Walsh, Daniel Krell, David Cabot, Linda Haston, Rick Kemp, Gayle Pazerski, Chelsea Mervis, and Ingrid Sonnichsen. Phographs by Stephen Kancianic.
  - The Crucible - Geneva College, 1977; 1.0 photograph
    The folder contains one photograph of Geneva College's production of The Crucible.
  - A Cry for Players, 1977; 4.0 photographs
    A Cry for Players was presented by the Community College of Allegheny County from April 30 - May 9, 1977. Photographs are of Jack Slotnik, Carole Campbell, James John Vecchio, Howard Kindal, Peter Keefer, Barbara Orwid, Marti Farmer Donovan, Linda Adinalfi, and Ray Leghart.
  - Cymbeline, 2008; 9.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    This file contains a CD-R disc with 9 images from Quantum Theatre's production of Cymbeline. The play was performed July 31st through August 24th, 2008 in Mellon Park. The images show actors Joel Ripka, Rick Kemp, Patrick Jordan, Mikelle Johnson, Mark Staley, David Whalen, and Sam Turich. Photographs by Heather Mull.
  - Da, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    Da was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from January 13 - February 19, 1984. Photograph is of G.W. Rooney and Robert Stoll.
  - Danger: Memory, 1987; 2.0 photographs
    Danger: Memory was presented by City Theatre from October 7 - November 1, 1987. Photographs are of Bill Dalzall, Bingo O'Malley, and Elsa Walden.
  - Dear Janet Rosenberg, Dear Mr. Kooning, 1979; 2.0 photographs
    Dear Janet Rosenberg, Dear Mr. Kooning was presented by the Pittsburgh Metropolitan Stage Company from May 3-12 and May 25-26, 1979. Photos are of J.P. Martin, and Susan Chapek.
  - Deathtrap, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    Deathtrap was presented by Mountain Playhouse from May 31 - June 12, 1983. This photograph is of Cheryl Moore, Henry Gardner, and David Anthony.
  - Deathtrap - Greensburg Civic Theater, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Greensburg Civic Theater's production of Deathtrap including Angelo Sembiante as Sidney Brohl.
  - Deathtrap, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Valley Players of Ligonier's production of Deathtrap including Art Bohlman.
  - The Decorator, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Deborah Sinclair and Jean Cardello. This Washington and Jefferson College Center Stage Players production was performed at W&J College. Photograph is dated July 24, 1995.
  - Diary of a Madman, Feb. 1979; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Mattress Factory's production of Diary of a Madman including Christopher Cooke.
  - The Dining Room, 1984; 1.0 photograph
    The Dining Room was presented by Pittsburgh Public Theater from May 25 - July 8, 1984. Photograph is of Gregg Almquist and William Carden.
  - Dirty Work at the Crossroads, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    Dirty Work at the Crossroads was presented by Robert Morris College Colonial Theater from May 28 - June 6, 1981. Photograph is of Pam McCready and Tom Gaydos.
  - The Doctor in Spite of Himself, 1975; 2.0 photographs
    The Doctor in Spite of Himself was presented by the Pittsburgh City Players in 1975. Photographs are of Geoffrey Hitch (Director) and Warren Bowles.
  - A Doll House, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    A Doll House was presented by the American Ibsen Theater from June 24 - August 19, 1983. Photograph is of Marina Coblentz and Rick Grove.
  - Don't Drink the Water, 1987; 1.0 photograph
    Don't Drink the Water was presented at Mountain Playhouse from July 7-19, 1987. This photograph is of cast members Jim Stream and Dick Scanlon.
  - Dracula, 1977; 6.0 photographs
    Dracula was presented by the Pittsburgh City Players from July 24 - August 23, 1977. Photographs are of Barbara Knowles, Ian Schneiderman, and Diane Heles.
  - Dracula: Sabbat, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    Dracula: Sabbat was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from January 15 - February 8, 1981. Photograph is of Dan Large and Maria Barney.
  - Driving Miss Daisy, 1990; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of the 1990 Mountain Playhouse production of Driving Miss Daisy. The photo shows Laurie Franks as Miss Daisy and Larnet Rutledge as Hoke. The play ran from October 3-14, 1990.
  - Driving Miss Daisy, 1999; 1.0 photograph
    Driving Miss Daisy was presented by the Mountain Playhouse from June 5-20, 1999. Photograph is of Peg French and Milton E. Thompson, Jr.
  - The Dumbwaiter, 1981; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of the Winter Company's production of The Dumbwaiter including David Butler and Ken Milchick.
  - The Dutch Courtesan, 1985; 1.0 photograph
    The Dutch Courtesan was presented by the American Ibsen Theater from July 12-27, 1985. Photograph is of Mark Gallagher and Kelly Hinman.
  - Dynamite Tonight, 1979; 2.0 photographs
    Dynamite Tonight was presented by Theatre Express from November 29 - December 16, 1979. Photographs are of cast members including Peter Matthey, John Ellerbrock, Ken Stribl, Jed Harris, and Claudia Zahn.
  - Einstein and the Polar Bear, 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Michael Anthony Safran, Rosemary Mizerak, and Dick Shannon. This Washington and Jefferson College Center Stage Players production was performed at W&J College. Photograph is dated June 12, 1995.
  - El Grande De Coca-Cola, 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one photograph of Oliver Plaza Dinner Theatre's production of El Grande De Coca-Cola including Mary Lee Casey, Jim Diedrich, David Green, and Lois Svoboda.
  - The Elephant Man, 1978; 1.0 photograph
    The Elephant Man was presented by Theatre Express from December 14, 1978 - January 7, 1979. Photograph is of Tom Spinella.
  - The Emperor's Nightingale, 1999; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two images of the 1999 Pittsburgh Playhouse's production of The Emperor's Nightingale.
  - Endgame, November 1989; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Robert Stoll and Glen Gress. This Laurel Highlands Regional Theatre production played from November 2-26, 1989.
  - The Entourage Music and Theatre Ensemble, 1976; 1.0 photograph
    The Entourage Music and Theatre Ensemble was presented by the 99 Cent Floating Theatre from October 28031, 1976. Photograph is of Ara Fitzgerald, Laurie Cameron, and Wall Matthews.
  - Equus, 1990; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph depicts a scene from Equus. This Laurel Highlands Regional Theatre production was performed from May 31 - June 24, 1990.
  - Everybody Loves Opal, September 1995; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph shows Mitch Kantor, Janet Dickinson, Dann Fink, and Joan Decker. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from September 6-17, 1995.
  - Evita - Gargaro Productions, 3.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Sandra Bargman and Anthony Marino. This production was performed at the Byham Theatre by Gargaro Productions.
  - Evita - Civic Light Opera, June 1991; 4.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Robert Michael Baker, Robert Alton, and Paige O'Hara. This Civic Light Opera (CLO) production was performed from June 18 - 30, 1991.
  - The Exonerated, 2006; 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two images from 2006 Pittsburgh Playhouse Repertory Company's production of The Exonerated. The first image features Doug Pona as David, David Cabot as Gary, and Joshua Elijah Reese as Robert. The second image features David Cabot as Gary. Photos courtesy of Drew Yenchak, Lighthouse Photography.
  - The Fall of the House of Usher, April 2001; 3.0 photographs
    Appearing in the photo are actors Mike Murray, Stacy Bartlebaugh-Gyms, Deborah Casciani, and Jay Smith. The Fall of the House of Usher was performed by the Edgar Allen Poe Theatre production company at the Gemini Theater, April 13-28, 2001. This was the first production by the company and featured a new adaptation of the Poe story by playwright/director Michael McGovern. Photos by George Mendel.
  - Fallen Angels, 1989; 1.0 photograph
    Fallen Angels was presented by the Pittsburgh Public Theater from February 21 - March 26, 1989. Photograph is of Simon Jutras.
  - Falsettos, 1997; 2.0 photographs
    Photographs are of Michael LaVolpe, Scott Robertson, Maureen Silliman, Barbara Pflaumer, and Barbara McCrane. This Pittsburgh Public Theater production was performed from January 9 - February 16, 1997.
  - The Fantasticks, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    The Fantasticks was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 16 - August 4, 2002. This photograph is of Douglas Rees, Susan J. Jacks, and David Garwood.
  - Father of the Bride - Comtra Theatre, 1.0 photograph
    This file contains one photograph from Comtra Theatre's production of Father of the Bride. Appearing in the photo are actors Dennis Broadhead as Mr. Massoula, Carrie Dagenhard as Kay Banks, Greg Evans as Buckly Dunstan, and Don Greca as Mr. Banks. The play was performed in March of an unknown year.
  - Father of the Bride - Mountain Playhouse, June 1992; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of David Garwood and Kelli Maguire. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed from June 16 - June 30, 1992.
  - Fences, 1989; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph shows Di Ray James and Monte Russell. This Pittsburgh Public Theater production was performed from May 23 - July 2, 1989.
  - Fiddler on the Roof - Gargaro Productions, 1997; 3.0 photographs
    This production of Fiddler on the Roof was performed from March 5 - 15, 1997 at the Byham Theatre by Gargaro Productions. Photographs are of Angela J. DeFilippo, Christy Marley, Sharon Connelly-Schaller, Howard Elson, and Susan Chapek.
  - Fiddler on the Roof - Camelot Productions, 1976; 2.0 photographs
    Fiddler on the Roof was presented by Camelot Productions from April 30 - May 30, 1976 at the Plaza Theatre. These photographs show Leonard Weitershausen and G. Fred Thickey.
  - Fiorello!, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    Fiorello! was presented by Civil Light Opera from June 22-27, 1993. Photograph is of Timothy Jerome.
  - Fires in the Mirror, 1995; 1.0 photograph
    Fires in the Mirror was presented by City Theatre from January 13 - February 5, 1995. Photograph is of Jennifer Mendenhall.
  - A Flea in Her Ear, 1990; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Ed Cain, Len Rolly, and Don Greca. This Comtra Theater production was performed January 11 - 27, 1990.
  - Floyd Collins, 2002; 1.0 photograph
    This folder contains one image of the 2002 Playhouse Conservatory Company's production of Floyd Collins. The image features Paul Pakler as Skeets Miller and Marcus Stevens as Floyd Collins. Photo courtesy of Lighthouse Photography.
  - The Flying Karamazov Brothers, 1983; 1.0 photograph
    The Flying Karamazov Brothers performed a vaudeville show at Stephen Foster Memorial Theatre from April 5-17, 1983.
  - Die Fledermaus, 2001; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Tim Hartman in the Pittsburgh Opera's 2000-2001 season production of Die Fledermaus.
  - The Footsteps of Doves, 2.0 photographs
    This folder contains two photographs of the Holiday Inn's production of The Footsteops of Doves including Jim coates, Vic Kleeman, and Mary Lou George.
  - For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf, April 2007; 3.0 photographs (on CD-R disc)
    This file contains a CD-R disc with 3 images from Point Park University's Conservatory Theatre Company production of For Colored Girls Who Have Considered Suicide When the Rainbow is Enuf. The play was performed April 12-22, 2007. The images show various members of the cast.
  - Forbidden Pittsburgh '88, 1988; 1.0 photograph
    Forbidden Pittsburgh '88 was presented by Don Brockett at the Green Tree Marriott from April 14 - June 25, 1988. Photograph is of Maggie Stewart and Chuck Aber.
  - Forbidden Pittsburgh '89, 1989; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of cast members from Forbidden Pittsburgh '89.
  - Forbidden Pittsburgh '93, 1993; 3.0 photographs
    Forbidden Pittsburgh '93 was presented by Don Brockett from May 4 - June 6, 1993 at Hartwood. Photographs are of Gorman Lowe, Phyllis Stern, Doug Mertz, Elizabeth Matthews, and Don Brockett.
  - The Foreigner, 1993; 1.0 photograph
    The Foreigner was presented by Mountain Playhouse from June 15-27, 1993. Photograph is of Nick Ruggeri and Jeff Skowron.
  - Forty Carats, 1972; 4.0 photographs
    Forty Carats was presented by the White Barn Theatre from May 23 - June 3, 1972. Photographs are of Bob Fitzpatrick, Cami Harper, Joe Matrozza, and Janet McDonald.
  - Foxfire, September 1991; 1.0 photograph
    Photograph is of Scott Wakefield, Deborah Rhodes, and David Garwood. This Mountain Playhouse production was performed September 18 - 29, 1991.
  - Frankie and Johnny in the Clair de Lune, 1988; 1.0 photograph
    Frankie and Johnny in the Clair de Lune was presented by City Theatre from October 5 - 30, 1988. Photograph is of Don Marshall and Susan Chapek.
  - Friedman & Son, 1977; 4.0 photographs
    Friedman & Son was presented by the Pittsburgh Laboratory Theatre from December 12-18, 1977. Photographs are of Mark Harris, Bob Fitzpatrick, and Bingo O'Malley.
  - Funny Money, 2003; 1.0 photograph
    Funny Money was presented by Mountain Playhouse from August 19-31, 2003. Photograph is of Nick Ruggeri and Susan J. Jacks.
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 2001; 4.0 photographs
    A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum was presented by Mountain Playhouse from July 17 - August 5, 2001. Photographs are of Nick Ruggeri, Neil A. Casey, Teclie Jo Smith, David Garwood, and Janet Dickinson.
  - Gardenia, 1986; 2.0 photographs
    Gardenia was presented by Pittsburgh Public Theater from April 15 - May 18, 1986. Photographs are of William Carden, Caryn West, Robert Desmond, and Steven Culp.
  - The Gazebo, 1985; 2.0 photographs
    The Gazebo was presented by the South Park Conservatory Theatre from July 5-21, 1985. Photographs are of Don Niggel, Phil Thompson, Larry Wineland, and Nick Schipani.
  - George Dandin, or the Confounded Husband, 1987; 2.0 photographs
    George Dandin, or the Confounded Husband was presented by Carnegie-Mellon University from June 17 - July 4 at the Kresge Theatre. These photographs are of cast members Elisabeth Orion, Eugene Troobnick, and Burt Edwards.
  - George Washington Slept Here, 1989; 2.0 photographs
    George Washington Slept Here was presented by Pittsburgh Public Theater from November 2 - December 17, 1989. Photograph is of Carey Cannon, Paul Marte, Brett Benner, Sabrina Reeves, William Parry, Barbara Broughton, and Donald Christopher.
  - Getting Out, 1982; 1.0 photograph
    Included in this file is a photograph of Mary Thomas, actress in the Fine Line Theatre Company's production of Getting Out. The play was staged from November 26th - December 19th, 1982.
  - The Gilded Age of Invention, 1979; 2.0 photographs
    The Gilded Age of Invention was presented by the Iron Clad Agreement on June 3, 1979. Photographs are of Christopher Josephs, K. Wilson Hutton, M.M. Melozzi, and James R. Krut.
  - The Gingerbread Lady, 1975; 1.0 photograph
    The Gingerbread Lady was presented by Chatham College from July 30 - August 17, 1975 at the Chatham College Theatre. This photograph is of cast members Herb Schacter, John Amplas, and Marianne McDermott.
  - The Glass Menagerie - Mountain Playhouse, 1994; 1.0 photograph
    The Glass Menagerie was presented by Mountain Playhouse from September 21 - October 2, 1994. Photograph is of Michael William McCarty and Jennifer Laura Thompson.
  - The Glass Menagerie - Prime Stage Theatre, March 2011; 4.0 photographs
    The Glass Menagerie was presented by Prime Stage Theatre March 5-13, 2011 at the New Hazlett Theater. The four photographs show actress Robin Walsh along with various other members of the cast.